The Beijing Asian Games are coming soon
and we will bring warmth with our Panda Panpan thermos.
[Shang Quanliang staff of the Security Section of the thermos factory]
This time,
the Panda Panpan thermos we co-produce
will bring the passion and warmth
to every household.
Look how pretentious Shang Quanliang is.
He's even taking notes.
Wow.
Our products will warm the Northeast
and the entire China.
[Celebration of Becoming the Licensed Thermos Manufacturer of the Asian Games and Safe Production Mobilization Meeting]
There will be a day
when our products are sold in Asia
and the entire world.
We shall prioritize
safety in production.
We shall not have accidents all year round.
[Can we forget the problems we have now by exploring alien civilizations?]
Safe production is the most important,
we have to remember that.
Do you think we can do it?
Yes!
[Good Guy Good Luck]
[Episode 1]
Bean sprout, please.
Okay. Bean sprout.
Chinese cabbage, please.
Okay.
Hey.
Quanliang.
Come and sit here.
Come on.
It's the same.
Sit here.
[UFO Research]
I see that you paid a lot of attention to the meeting just now.
You were even taking notes.
You'll be the one who ensures
our accident-free production in the future.
Accident-free production all year round
is not difficult.
I had three accident-free years
when I worked as a driver in the provincial capital.
How long did you work there?
Ten years.
Then I'd rather call it
seven years with accidents.
When there's no common ground, it's useless to talk.
I'm leaving.
Is this the Hospital of Liuhe County?
I want to speak to Dr. Shang Jin.
Wait a moment.
I'll find her.
Thank you.
Hello.
Jin,
this is dad.
Um,
Sunday is coming.
Will you go home?
You haven't been home for several months.
[Shang Jin Doctor of the Hospital of Liuhe County]
What do you want to eat? I'll cook it for you.
I'll go home if there are no patients.
Okay.
Tell me before you come back then.
I'll pick you up at the bus station.
You don't need to. I can return by myself.
Dr. Shang!
I'm busy. Goodbye.
What do you want...
Leave it there.
If you like it, ask your parents for money to buy it.
Behave yourselves.
Get out of here!
[New Books]
The books wear out
because of these naughty kids.
How can I sell them?
Quanliang, don't you think so?
Stop! Police here!
[Hu Ting Detective of the Criminal Police
of the Municipal Public Security Bureau]
Stop!
I came here to look for my sister
and I happened to see you showering.
How dare you peep at me when I was showering?
Freeze!
Freeze! Police here!
Stop!
Freeze!
Come down!
Dayu, come on.
It aches all over.
Doctor,
hurry up. Give him an injection.
Now my father is the one who got injured.
Did you see him? He's old!
Now he's seriously injured,
who can take the responsibility?
Can you?
If you can't,
find someone who can, okay?
Come on! Who can take the responsibility?
Did you see how serious my father's injury is?
Listen,
[Mr. Liu Chief of the Criminal Police of the Municipal Public Security Bureau]
drop the act!
I just don't understand.
You were just asked to catch a thief.
How did you mess it up?
I'll see them and explain it then.
You'd better not. Don't make it even harder.
Go back and write a report now.
Every day you bring me new problems.
[Xueqin's Dumplings]
Hello, Quanliang. You're off duty?
What kind of dumplings do you want?
I'll make them for you now.
Mixed vegetable dumplings, your signature dish.
This one?
Okay.
I'll peel the garlic.
[Xueqin Owner of the dumpling restaurant]
What stories are you reading?
Not stories,
but scientific knowledge.
What scientific knowledge? Tell me about it.
Recently, there's big news
in the scientific community indeed.
That is, the global human genome project
has been launched.
What is genome?
Genome is something that decides
human beings' health and character,
and it's invisible to the naked eye.
Its shape is like...
A bit like this.
I'll show you.
It looks like...
Like this.
Fried dough twist?
Xueqin, you're so smart.
I haven't thought of this
after such a long time.
Dayu, what's up?
I'm okay.
Dayu!
I'm fine!
You got into a fight again?
Such
a naughty boy.
Teenage boys
are all like this. Forget about it.
He's my only younger brother.
I have to take care of him.
Quanliang,
you told me last time
that the thermos factory might hire Dayu.
How's that going?
I... I've got a new idea.
I'll tell you when there's progress.
Okay. Thank you.
You're welcome.
I'll cook the dumplings for you now.
Okay.
Mr. Hu, someone wants to see you.
Come in.
Uncle.
Why did you come late at night?
Why did I come?
You work late every day. I'm here to bring you food.
You haven't had dinner, have you?
Here you are. Dumplings and liquor.
Dumplings are fine,
but not liquor.
Let me see.
I happen to be hungry now.
Nice.
Um,
are you here
because you want me to help you?
Of course
I'm here to visit you.
I heard
that the public security bureau is recruiting.
Just temporary workers.
Not permanent.
Is there an age requirement?
I think not. How old is that person?
Born in 1938, in his early 50s.
You?
Can I do it?
What's up?
You don't want to work
for the thermos factory anymore?
Put in a good word for me please.
Excuse me.
Hello.
Hello, Ting.
I'm at the hospital.
They gave him an examination
and there are no serious problems.
He'll be discharged in two days.
Okay. Thank you.
See, the cap fits me.
It fits my head.
What are you doing, uncle?
The police cap doesn't look good on a shaved head.
If I can work for the police,
I'll grow my hair
just like yours, okay?
Take the cap off.
I promise.
Take it off. Or others may see you
and it will be
embarrassing.
What happened?
It's okay. Something about work.
You're on the night shift every day,
and Ling is at home by herself. Is she okay?
Yes. She's long got used to it.
Got used to it.
That's not a good thing.
Okay.
How about you eat dumplings and stop talking?
Help yourself.
I bought them for you.
[Crack Down on Crime to Maintain Public Order]
Sir, I wonder if you could do me a favor.
My uncle...
Hu Ting,
I was going to talk to you.
What's up?
The Director said the Register Office
is understaffed at the moment.
You can go help them
sort the documents.
As for when you'll return,
let's wait and see.
What do you mean?
Do you still remember
that an old man was hospitalized because of you?
But he's not seriously injured.
I don't know if he is,
but his family is complaining
and asking you for compensation in the hospital.
I... I was trying to catch a thief, sir.
Where is the thief then?
I was also trying to catch the person
who showed obscene videos.
So where are the videos?
What...
Look.
You mistook a person for someone else last time.
That person ended up in hospital
and you had to offer compensation.
It happened not so long ago, right?
Sir, it's been months.
How can you be
so stubborn?
Listen,
go to the hospital now
and apologize to him earnestly.
This matter can only be settled
when he forgives you.
If you get into trouble again,
you'll be fired. Understand?
Go now!
Come back!
What's up this time?
You came to see me, didn't you?
What's up?
Nothing!
Go now!
Buy some gifts!
What's up, Ting?
I got promoted.
Is that bigger than yours?
Two kings.
Follow or not?
I won.
I won. Two jokers.
I won. No cards left.
Give me money.
We're a family.
Are you giving me money?
- Son.
- We're a family...
Give me money. You lost.
So you're playing cards?
Why are you here?
Ask your boss to come.
We'll only talk to him.
Right.
[Crown Dance Hall]
Who?
An old man is hospitalized
because Hu Ting struck him?
Yeah.
How did you know that?
My neighbor Meng
works in the hospital.
She knows everything there.
[Lyu Ling Shop assistant of the Department Store]
Then how serious
is
his injury?
He's fine.
He just wants to stay in hospital for longer
so he can blackmail Hu Ting.
I mean, will Hu Ting be unhappy
when you return home late?
He returns home even later than I do.
Really?
I envy you.
I'll marry a policeman too.
Min,
have you ever had feelings like this?
Nothing serious, but I just feel bored.
It's hard for me to breathe and I want to cry.
What's wrong?
Is everything okay between you and Hu Ting?
Yes.
The next song is "Time to Wake Up"
requested by Table No. 7.
It's your song.
Let's applaud.
[Bian Diwu Owner of the Crown Dance Hall]
[Zhao Changhai Subordinate of Bian Diwu]
♪You said you've loved the wrong person♪
♪And you've been hurt♪
♪You said you've made mistakes you should never make♪
♪And you regretted it♪
♪You said you've gone through all the difficulties♪
♪And you didn't know who to trust♪
♪You said you felt so upset♪
♪And you even questioned yourself♪
♪If you'd known that sadness was inevitable♪
♪Maybe you wouldn't have been so devoted♪
♪Love is always unforgettable♪
♪That little warmth is unnecessary♪
♪Sadness is always inevitable♪
♪It comes when you wake up♪
♪There's something you don't have to ask now♪
♪And there's someone you never have to wait for♪
[Sunday]
Sunday comes.
Jin will come home today.
Doctor, help!
Help!
Doctor!
Doctor, help!
Help!
- That's so scary.
- What's that?
Help!
That's horrifying.
Save him!
What's wrong?
Please help.
He went to Laoyao Mountain today
and returned like this.
And he has
all these strange things on his skin.
Those lumps.
Dr. Shang,
the patient is twitching.
Blood oxygen level is dropping.
[Telephone]
Can I speak to Dr. Shang, Shang Jin?
She has left.
When did she leave?
She left in a hurry.
She took the earliest bus to the provincial capital.
Why did she go to the provincial capital?
I don't know that.
Do you know Sun?
The bearded carpenter working in the tree farm.
He likes to drink.
When he was drunk, he'd start a fight with his wife.
Last year, he was fired
and he began to drink even more.
In the end, his wife left.
She left with another guy?
When she left, she took all the money with her.
She only left ten yuan for their son.
The women today are so cruel.
When the marriage goes south, they will leave.
I heard that the wife of Shang Quanliang,
a security guard of our factory, has also left him.
Shang Quanliang?
Yeah.
Otherwise he wouldn't have left
the provincial capital for Shuangyuhe.
His wife cheated on him
and everyone at his workplace knew it.
Quanliang felt so ashamed
that he came here with his daughter.
I heard that he and his daughter are not close.
[Eight years ago 1982 The provincial capital]
What are you doing?
Smoking?
My mom won't spare you later.
Mom.
Mom!
Dad!
Where is mom?
Where is mom? I'm asking you.
I kicked her out.
Hui, it's far,
let's take turns driving.
It's okay, sir.
I can do it.
Sir!
Hurry up!
A round trip to Shuangyuhe takes hours.
Okay.
I drove the car here without telling anyone.
I have to return it to the factory before dawn.
Where is Jin?
I'll find her.
Why do I have to leave the big city
for Shuangyuhe?
You have to follow your father.
Go.
I won't!
Why did you kick mom out?
Get her back.
I'll go if she goes.
Stop the nonsense.
Let's go.
Get mom back!
You can't get it, can you?
Don't use chopsticks,
use your hand instead.
Just use your hand. Come on.
Ting.
These years...
These years are difficult for me.
What's wrong?
I'm all alone.
How?
You still have me and Jin.
Has Jin come home recently?
In my opinion,
you should tell Jin the truth.
Her mother left home herself,
you didn't kick her out.
How can I tell her this?
Why can't you?
If her mother comes back in the future,
how can they two face each other?
I'll be the bad guy.
Why do you have to be the bad guy?
You're old now.
You're not as strong as you think.
I...
Please...
Please let me
get the job in the public security bureau.
So I can feel proud.
I'm begging you.
Here's to you.
Please don't.
- Please don't.
- Here's to you.
Please no.
Here's to you.
Goodness me.
Uncle,
I'll be honest.
Recently
I got into trouble too.
Mind the steps.
Take care.
Take care on your way home.
Be careful.
What can I do to help you?
You?
You don't need to help.
Just don't cause me trouble.
Don't be angry.
I won't.
Actually, I know
what you can do to get the job.
Make a contribution.
Make a contribution?
Last time, the bureau specifically asked
the warehouse keeper
of the department store to work there.
I think he caught two thieves in the store.
After he came, he received a third-class merit too.
He got a decent amount of money award.
I don't care about that.
Um,
does catching thieves count as a contribution?
Of course.
Catching thieves or hooligans,
and helping others bravely all count.
If you can make a contribution,
I'll put in a good word for you too.
Then I think
there's hope for you to get the job.
Great.
Okay.
When there's a chance, I'll tell you.
Let's work together.
Uncle, forget about it.
Listen to me and take care of yourself.
You'll do me a big favor by doing that.
You're in trouble too, aren't you?
I'm okay.
Not a big deal.
Okay.
Take care.
Can you make it home?
Oh, stop.
Look.
There are stairs...
There are curbs ahead. Be careful.
I'm prepared. Look.
It's bumpy.
Such an eccentric man.
Go home.
Brother.
Here you are.
The woman who danced here
a few days ago wanted to resign.
I rejected her.
This is her bag.
Have the Tiger Brothers left?
When will they reach Laoyao Mountain?
They'll reach the border tomorrow.
[Border]
[Tiger Brothers Stowaways]
Shuangyuhe is such a peaceful place.
Everyone here is a law-abiding citizen.
Huh?
Isn't that good?
The Asian Games are coming soon.
But I hope to work.
As a security guard,
now I have nothing to do.
Boy, come here.
Who are you looking for?
Liu Yongli, who works in the 4th Workshop.
Who are you?
I'm his little brother.
I was robbed,
I need his help.
Where? Who did that?
In the billiard room.
I was robbed and beaten
by three middle school students.
Look.
I'll help you then.
Stay where you are.
Don't move.
I'll get the bicycle.
I'm going to help the boy
and get rid of the bad guys.
Sir, can you do it?
There are three of them.
Why should I be afraid?
Good always prevails over evil.
How about we ask my brother to go with us?
Don't bother.
If we arrive late, maybe they've run away.
Are these two the guys who robbed you?
No.
The three guys in the back did it.
Are they middle school students?
They are.
They're wrestlers of the sports school.
I see.
I'll ask my brother to come.
Boy, you don't need to.
Don't worry.
You came here to help him,
old guy?
Yes.
So what?
I'm the one who robbed him.
And I slapped him in the face.
So what?
If I want, I can rob you too.
I'm a security guard of the thermos factory.
Now I'll talk to you
on behalf of your parents.
Although you practice martial arts
and wrestling,
you can't bully the weak.
You're the future of our country,
I hope you can grow up to be
all-round...
Okay, old guy.
I'll just put the money here.
Do you think he dares to take it?
Take it.
Take it!
That's your money. Take it.
Good prevails over evil. Why not...
I'm a security guard.
Don't ask for it.
Come on.
Boy,
take the wallet
out of my back pocket.
There's five yuan inside,
that's yours.
I don't want it.
Take it.
Don't tell this
to your brother.
I'm too embarrassed to tell him.
Quanliang,
do you want me to light it up for you?
No, I've quit smoking.
Why are you holding a cigarette then?
I enjoy looking at it.
You like doing that?
Better eat snacks instead.
Do you have books
about practicing strength
to punch above one's weight?
[Impenetrable Defense]
Qigong.
You can punch above your weight with that.
[Intensive Care]
Darling,
thank you for taking care of me.
Here, tangerine for you.
Help yourself.
You've had a hard time,
haven't you?
Here you are.
Nice.
Here.
Brother.
Why isn't there a railway in our village?
Those from Rabbit Tail Ravine
go to the railway line to steal coal every day.
I wanted to get some too
but they kicked me out.
Didn't the vigilantes stop them?
The vigilantes are their relatives.
No one will do anything.
Take it easy.
Hemorrhoid surgery is so painful.
I can hardly move.
The vigilantes didn't do anything,
then how about the police?
No one called the police.
The police didn't know it.
Tomorrow is Sunday and I'll study Qigong at home.
Will you come?
No. I'll be on a mission.
You work in the Register Office now, don't you?
So what?
I can't work there forever.
I'm going to catch the thieves.
Catch the thieves?
Yes, the coal thieves.
To the locomotive depot?
Of course not.
The thieves are not as bold as that.
I'm going to the Rabbit Tail Ravine.
I'm very familiar with the terrain there.
I can show you the way.
You don't need to. I can go by myself.
You're going alone?
I heard
the clue myself.
I thought I could redeem myself.
I...
I can't stand working in the Register Office,
you know?
That's one more reason for me to go.
I'll bring a shotgun.
What shotgun?
You often say that
you arm yourself with knowledge, don't you?
You can just bring your knowledge.
I'll try to convince them.
I'll focus on changing their views.
We two together
will make a great contribution.
[Pingdingshan Township, Shuangyuhe]
Look at your outfit.
I want a sense of ceremony.
Did you bring your weapon with you?
Should I bring it?
I'll go get...
I mean, your knowledge.
Yes.
Get on.
Okay.
Be careful.
Ting,
we need to think of some tactics.
Another crazy idea.
Why do we need them?
What if they fight back?
Who will?
If they fight back, let's fix them.
We can't be too straightforward.
Think of some strategies,
For example, concealing our intentions,
luring them away,
escaping secretly
or using drastic measures. What do you think?
What did you say?
So you missed it all.
Ting,
Remember,
be bold and careful, don't panic.
Be calm.
Steady yourself.
Freeze!
What are you doing?
Police!
What police? You're not even wearing uniforms.
Plainclothes police!
- They're fake.
- Beat them.
Beat them.
That's a real gun.
Stop!
Ting! Be careful!
Be careful.
Ting!
I told you to be careful.
Look, now you're injured.
What are you doing?
Whose side are you on?
What side?
Why were you yelling just now?
I said we needed to conceal our intentions,
didn't I?
You mean, you wanted them to attack me?
No...
What I meant was,
I'd ask them to stop moving
and you'd rush to catch them.
I'd guard the scene of crime
and you'd catch all the criminals.
I did my job well,
how did you get injured?
I've told you so on the motorcycle,
but you pretended that you couldn't hear me.
[Laowu Member of the criminal gang Tiger Brothers]
Uncle, you're lucky that I'm the one with you.
What you did just now
is illegal. Understand?
You're lashing out desperately.
Let's go!
What should I do with their tools
used to steal coal?
Take them with you!
What can I do with them?
Making a fire!
You're angry because of shame.
I'm angry too.
Why did Laowu get off in advance?
He has the money and the gun with him.
[Dahu Member of the criminal gang Tiger Brothers]
We have to finish our business first.
Wait until we reach Shuangyuhe.
♪A rusty gun♪
♪Won't be handy anymore♪
♪And a nostalgic person♪
♪Won't be as passionate as before♪
♪Pretending♪
♪Is even harder than lying♪
♪Do you know♪
♪I'm vulnerable too♪
♪A healed wound♪
♪Still hurts♪
♪How can I go on♪
♪When she's not here anymore♪
♪Forgetting♪
♪Is even harder than loving♪
♪Do you know♪
♪I still have something to tell♪
♪High and low♪
♪We drift in the crowd♪
♪Confused, we rise and fall♪
♪Only when there's no one around♪
♪Dare I be honest♪
♪And cry as much as I want♪
♪Every time I think of you again♪
♪I will still be nervous♪
♪It turns out that you've become♪
♪An old scar on my chest♪
♪You're an old scar on my chest♪